Guide to the George Washington University Publications collection, 1924-2017 RG0154
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Science and Biology, Series 21
  - Part I: Aquatic Biologists of the World and Their Laboratories, May 1964; Series 21 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Part II: Aquatic Biologists of the World and Their Laboratories, May 1964; Series 21 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - The News Publication as a Medium of Scientific Communication, January 1964; Series 21 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Education and Training Opportunitites for Information Scientists: 1959-1963, Series 21 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Space Biology and Space Bioscience Resources, February 15, 1964; Series 21 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Basic Library List for the Biological Sciences, March 1969; Series 21 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Education in the Boiological Sciences: Teaching and Research, May 1969; Series 21 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - The Pre-service Preparation of Secondary School Biology Teachers, June 1969; Series 21 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Biology in the Two Year College, April 1969; Series 21 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Software Reliability, April 23, 1984; Series 21 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Software Performance Measurement of Computer Generated Programs, Undated; Series 21 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Widget (Waterloo Interactive Debugging Job Entry Terminal) User's Manual, July 1979; Series 21 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Coroutine-based Implementation of Nonprocedural Programming Languages, August 1983; Series 21 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Programming Languages in the Soviet Union, April 1984; Series 21 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - State Vector Domains and Denotational Semantic Definitions, August 1984; Series 21 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - A Binary Tree for Pattern Closeness Search, August 1984; Series 21 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - State Vector Semantics of Block Structure Languages, August 1984; Series 21 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Proceedings of the George Washington University Seminar on Neural Networks, 1992; Series 21 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Can Ada (*) be a Standard Language for Medical Information Processing?, April 1984; Series 21 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Ada (*) at the George Washington University: Experiences and Observations, April 1984; Series 21 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Small Ada Parallel Monitoring, May 1991; Series 21 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Small Ada PC Integrated Environment, July 1991; Series 21 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - GWEd: A Full Screen Editor for AdaEd, September 1992; Series 21 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Ada in a Very Large CS1 Course, January 1993; Series 21 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - A Programming Language with Automatic Goal Generation and Selection, 1970; Series 21 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Information Hiding in Pascal: Packages and Pointers, March 1981; Series 21 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Towards a Fail-safe Approach to Secure Databases, January 10, 1980; Series 21 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Methods and Applications of Time Series Analysis Part I: REgression, Trends, Smoothing, and Differencing, July 24, 1980; Series 21 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Time Series Analysis and Forecasting of Failure Rate Processes, December 16, 1974; Series 21 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - A Time Series Analysis of Some Interrelated Logistics Performance Variables, November 4, 1981; Series 21 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Detecting the Shift in the Probability of Success in a Series of Bernoulli Trials, June 23, 1977; Series 21 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Averaging Time and Maxima for Dependent Observations, December 20, 1972; Series 21 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Availability and Readiness Using Transfer Function Models and Cross Spectral Analysis, March 29, 1978; Series 21 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Improvement of Kernal Estimators of the Failure Rate Function Using the Generalized Jackknife, February 14, 1980; Series 21 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Approximate Bayes Solutions to the Inventory Problem, January 7, 1974; Series 21 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Classical Bayesian Approaches to the Change-point Problem: Fixed Sample and Sequential Procedures, July 1979; Series 21 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - A Bayes Empirical Bayes Approach for (Software) Reliability Growth, April 13, 1984; Series 21 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Bayesian Inference for the Weibull Process with Applications to Assessing Software Reliability Growth and Predicting Software Failures, April 14, 1984; Series 21 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Monitoring the Reliability of Pershing II Missiles: A Critique of the Current Methodology and a Suggested Combined Bayesian-sample Theoretic Approach, April 12, 1984; Series 21 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - A Bayesian Assessment of Cherent Structures, January 14, 1974; Series 21 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Computer Programs for "A Bayesian Approach to Quantile and Response Probability Estimation Using Binary Response Data": A User's Guide, January 4, 1982; Series 21 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - An Application of Empirical Bayes Techniques to the Simultaneous Estimation of Many Probabilities, May 3, 1984; Series 21 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Some Bayesian Approaches for Estimating the Failure Rate, May 31, 1982; Series 21 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - A Bayesian Approach to Quantile and Response Probability Estimation with Applications in Reliability, April 11, 1984; Series 21 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - An Examination of Risk Analysis Methodologies, March 1983; Series 21 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Convergence Properties of Local Solutions of Sequences of Mathematical Programming Problems in General Spaces, December 1971; Series 21 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - The U.S. Army (BRL's) Kinetic Energy Penetrator Problem: Estimating the Probability of Response for a Given Stimulus, December 21, 1981; Series 21 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - The Kalman Filter Approach to Accelerated Life Testing: A Preliminary Development, May 28, 1982; Series 21 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Understanding the Kalman Filter, October 14, 1981; Series 21 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - The Design of a Quantal Response Experiment: An Empirical Approach, April 18, 1983; Series 21 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Representation and Solution of Decision Problem Using Sequential Diagrams, 1995; Series 21 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Sequential Diagrams and Influence Diagrams: A Complimentary Relationship for Modeling and Solving Decision Problems, 1995; Series 21 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Exploratory Evaluation of the Accuracy of Linguistic vs. Numeric Risk Assessment of Computer Security, May 1981; Series 21 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Tree-based Risk Analysis Using Inexact Estimates, June 24, 1981; Series 21 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Comparison of Properties of Three Estimators of the Parameter of a Poisson Distribution Truncated Below One, When the Sample Size is Small, August 8, 1975; Series 21 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Computing the Value of the Maximum Likelihood Estimate of the Parameter of a Poisson Distribution Truncated Below One, August 8, 1975; Series 21 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Some Contributions to the Methodology for Analyzing Failure Data, May 7, 1978; Series 21 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Effective Statistical Test for Detection Models, February 17, 1972; Series 21 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Some Statistic Characterizations of Multivariate Survival, July 18, 1975; Series 21 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - The Analysis of Contingency Tables: A Methodological Exposition, May 21, 1973; Series 21 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - An Empirical Comparison of Typological Analysis Methods, July 18, 1975; Series 21 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Reliability Calculation Using Randomization for Markovian Fault-Tolerant Computing Systems, October 29, 1982; Series 21 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - A Poisson Process Approximation For Generalized K-S Confidence Regions, November 19, 1982; Series 21 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - An Introduction to Mathmatical Statistics: A One Semester Program for Engineers and Physical Scientists, December 1966; Series 21 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - A Unified Model for Demand Prediction in the Context of Provisioning and Procurement, May 5, 1971; Series 21 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Data Structures with Ada, 1993; Series 21 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Report on Task II: Identification of Affected Parties, June 11, 1975; Series 21 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Environmental Pollution Control System with Energy Recovery and Water Reclamation, June 1977; Series 21 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Benefit-cost Techniques for Public Water and Sewer Projects, September 1969; Series 21 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Water Supply Management in the District of Columbia: An Institutional Assessment, February 1982; Series 21 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration: Ocean Engineering Technology Transfer Operation, March 24, 1978; Series 21 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Wildlife Movements and Tracking Systems: Bibliography, September 1970; Series 21 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Bibliography of Products Derived from Aquatic Organisms, August 1971; Series 21 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Scientific Publications of the Bioscience Programs Division, NASA: Behavioral Biology (Volume 1), 1967; Series 21 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Scientific Publications of the Bioscience Programs Division, NASA: Environmental Biology (Volume 2), 1967; Series 21 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Scientific Publications of the Bioscience Programs Division, NASA: Exobiology (Volume 3), 1967; Series 21 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Scientific Publications of the Bioscience Programs Division, NASA: Physical Biology (Volume 4), 1967; Series 21 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Scientific Publications of the Bioscience Programs Division, NASA: Planetary Quarantine and Bioscience Communications (Vols. 5 and 6), 1967; Series 21 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Evaluation of the Use of Nuclear Science Abstracts, September 30, 1965; Series 21 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - A World of Nuclear Power?, May 1967; Series 21 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Espionage and Security Leaks: Diagnosis and Therapy, May 1985; Series 21 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Strategies for Manipulating: Universal Decimal Classification Relationships for Computer Retrieval, December 1970; Series 21 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Effectiveness of the NSF International Travel Grant Program, March 15, 1976; Series 21 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Final Report on Executive Development at Redstone Arsenal, April 15, 1954; Series 21 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - The Pentagon Seminar: "Techniques of Personnel Assessment", Undated; Series 21 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Constant-area Flow Interactions in Cryptosteady-flow Thrust Augmenters: Part 1, April 1977; Series 21 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Constant-area Flow Interactions in Cryptosteady-flow Thrust Augmenters: Part 2, April 1977; Series 21 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - The Effects of Weight-Fluctuations on the Performance of Null-Steering Adaptive Arrays, April 1984; Series 21 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Active/Passive Control of Civil Engineering Structures Subjected to Environmental Loads, September 5, 1981; Series 21 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Stocastic Response of Tall Structures Under Environmental Loads: Final Report Part III, Technical Info., August 1981; Series 21 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Active Control of Structures Under Earthquake and Other Dynamic Loads, June 25, 1984; Series 21 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Proceeding of the Sypmosium on Welding, Bonding, and Fastening, June 1972; Series 21 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Title III in Environmental Education, 1972; Series 21 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - A Comparative Study of Lawn Irrigation Systems for the General Services Administration, December 28, 1966; Series 21 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - A Literature Survey of Benchmark Pesticides, March 1976; Series 21 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Improvement of Models for Multi-disciplinary Systems, March 1971; Series 21 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Nonlinear Programming Sensitivity Analysis Results Using Strong Second Order Assumptions, June 26, 1978; Series 21 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Sensitivity Analysis for Nonlinear Programming Using Penalty Methods: Technical Report, March 7, 1973; Series 21 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Basic Results in the Development of Sensitivity and Stability Analysis in Constrained Mathematical Programming, August 7, 1979; Series 21 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Computational Experience with Optimal Value Function and Lagrange Multiplier Sensitivity in NLP, May 10, 1976; Series 21 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Computational Experience in Sensitivity Analysis for Nonlinear Programming, February 22, 1973; Series 21 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Exact Sensitivity Analysis Using Augmented Lagrangians, March 22, 1977; Series 21 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - A Guide to a Sumt-version 4 Computer Subroutine for Implementing Sensitivity Analysis in Nonlinear Programming, July 9, 1973; Series 21 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Sensitivity Analysis for RHS Perturbations: A Brief Survey and Second-order Extensions, April 20, 1976; Series 21 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Second-order Parametric Sensitivity Analysis in NLP and Estimates by Penalty Function Methods, December 4, 1975; Series 21 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - A Separable Programming Approach to the Linear Complementary Problem, June 22, 1979; Series 21 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Infinitely Constrained Optimization Problems, June 28, 1974; Series 21 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - A Nonconvex Max-min Problem, September 12, 1974; Series 21 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - On Solving a Dynamic Optimal Budgeting Problem, June 9, 1983; Series 21 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - An Algorithm for Locating Approximate Global Solutions of Nonconvex, Separable Problems, April 20, 1972; Series 21 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - For Concave Minimization Problems, April 10, 1975; Series 21 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Use of a Stable Generalized Inverse Algorithm to Evaluate Newton Method Strategies, October 25, 1978; Series 21 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Extensions of the Gauvin-Tolle Optimal Value Differential Stability Results to General Mathematical Problems, April 20, 1979; Series 21 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Sharper Bounds on Nonconvex Programs, May 15, 1973; Series 21 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Convexity and Concavity Properties of the Optimal Value Function in Parametic Nonlinear Programming, December 21, 1982; Series 21 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Generalized Convexity and Concavity Properties of the Optimal Value Function in Parametric Nonlinear Programming, April 11, 1983; Series 21 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Computability of Global Solutions to Factorable Nonconvex Programs: Convex Underestimating Problems (Part I), January 7, 1975; Series 21 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Computing Bounds on the Location of an Isolated Local Minimizer, December 6, 1977; Series 21 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Convergence Theory for Unconstrained Minimization, September 30, 1980; Series 21 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Second Order Convergence Using a Modified Armijo Step-size Rule for Function Minimization, January 15, 1976; Series 21 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Strategies for the Minimization of an Unconstrained Nonconvex Function, November 1976; Series 21 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Locating an Isolated Global Minimizer of a Constrained Nonconvex Program, September 27, 1979; Series 21 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - An Idealized Exact Penalty Function, July 14, 1977; Series 21 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Large Scale Nonlinear Programming, June 15, 1978; Series 21 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - On the Convergence and Rate of Convergence of the Conjugate Gradient Method, May 16, 1972; Series 21 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Interactive Branch-and-bound Algorithm for Multiple Criteria Optimization, May 31, 1981; Series 21 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - The Design of Multiactivity Multifacility Systems, June 15, 1981; Series 21 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Near-optimum Design of Large-scale Systems, April 1985; Series 21 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - A Steady-state Version of a Dynamic Optimal Budgeting Problem, April 16, 1984; Series 21 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Fourier Integral Estimate of the Failure Rate Function and its Mean Square Error Properties, March 14, 1980; Series 21 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - An Empirically Developed Fourier Series Model for Describing Software Failures, November 17, 1982; Series 21 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Radiation Transfer Processes in Particulate Laden Combustor Flows: Final Report FY 1978, May 31, 1979; Series 21 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Radiation Transfer Processes in Particulate Laden Combustor Flows: Final Report FY 1979, February 26, 1981; Series 21 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Radiation Transfer Processes in Particulate Laden Combustor Flows: Final Report, May 31, 1979; Series 21 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Our Physical Heritage, 1935; Series 21 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Medicine and Health Topics, Series 22
  - Historical Sketch of the Medical School: 1825-1947, October 1947; Series 22 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Design for Medical Education: The Development and Planning of a Medical College and Care Center, February 1965; Series 22 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Conference for Foreign Scholars in the Medical Sciences Program on "Medical Education in the United States", June 16, 1968; Series 22 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Final Progress Report: Special Project Grant 03D-005014-03 for the Development of Programs in Primary Care, 1977; Series 22 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Hospices, 1982; Series 22 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - State Laws Related to Hospice Care Programs, 1979; Series 22 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Basic Support Technology for Medical Signal Processing, 1972-1973; Series 22 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Profiles of the States and Health Care Reform: Prepared for the Henry J. Kaiser Family Foundation, July 1993; Series 22 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Report and Bibliography on the Delivery of Health Care with Special Emphasis on Utilization Review, September 30, 1971; Series 22 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Study of Innovative Transportation in Health Care Delivery: Ground Transportation, June 1973; Series 22 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Mental Health: Administration, 1979; Series 22 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Mental Health Benefits Under Medicaid: A Survey of the States, January 1984; Series 22 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Working with Cerebral Palsy, February 1981; Series 22 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Hemiplegia: Current Approaches to Patient Positioning, 1979; Series 22 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Infectious Meningitis: An Annotated Bibliography of the World Literature, 1964-1970, on Neisseria meningitidis, March 1971; Series 22 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - The Blood-bubble Interactions in Decompression Sickness: An Annotated Bibliography, February 1973; Series 22 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - A Proposal to Establish a Resource Center for Educational Program Development in Cancer Research, April 28, 1976; Series 22 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Evaluation of Auditory Comprehension Impairment in Adult Aphasia, February 26, 1977; Series 22 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Evaluation and Treatment of Apraxia of Speech and Dysathria, February 1976; Series 22 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - GW Greensheet: George Washington University Hospital, 1970-1974; Series 22 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Greensheet: George Washington University Hospital, 1974-1978; Series 22 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Greensheet: George Washington University Hospital, January 1979; Series 22 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Legistlative Snapshot: Certificate of Need, Undated; Series 22 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - A Feasibility Study for a National Rehabilitation Information Center, 1975; Series 22 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Travel for the Patient with Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease, Undated; Series 22 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Biological Prerequisites for Education in the Health Sciences, June 1969; Series 22 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Manual on Educational Programs for Administrators of Long-term Health Care Facilities, May 1966; Series 22 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Report to the Maryland State Department of Health on the Curriculum Development Program for Long-term Care Administration in the State of Maryland, May 1966; Series 22 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - An Investigation of Modeling for Health Policy: Final Report of Grant Number CP-T-000106-01-0, August 1975; Series 22 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Some Philosphical Dimensions of Administration: The Merck Sharp and Dohme Lecture Series in Health Care Administration, May 1964; Series 22 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - The Public Health Guidelines Governing Research Involving Human Subjects: An Analysis of the Policy-making Process, February 1972; Series 22 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Health Planning Impementation: Concepts from the Social Sciences and Marketing within a Theoretical Framework, December 3, 1975; Series 22 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Coordination of Regulatory Authority: A Survey of the States, May 2, 1980; Series 22 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Report on the District of Columbia Behavioral Risk Factor Survey: June 1982, July 1983; Series 22 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - National Survey of State HIV/AIDS Funds: FY 1992, April 1993; Series 22 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Alternatives to Institutional Care for the Elderly: An Analysis of State Initiatives, September 1981; Series 22 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Environmental Protection for Health Promotion, May 1981; Series 22 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Home Health Care, 1980; Series 22 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Study of Innovative Transportation in Health Care Delivery: Air Transport, November 1972; Series 22 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Education for Health Services Administrators of the Future: Final Report of Contract Number N01-MB-44177, August 1976; Series 22 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Current and Emerging Issues in Public Health Policy, September 1983; Series 22 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - State Health Promotion and Disease Prevention Initiatives, 1983; Series 22 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - The Use of HMOs by State Employees, Undated; Series 22 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Medigap: Issues and Update, June 1982; Series 22 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Medigap: State Responses to Problems with Health Insurance for the Elderly, October 30, 1979; Series 22 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - A Review of State Indigent Care Programs: 1992, December 1992; Series 22 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - A Review of State Task Force and Special Study Recommendations to Address Health Care for the Idigent, November 1984; Series 22 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Delivery of Health Care Services in Less Developed Coutnries with Emphasis on Integration of Family Planning with Maternal and Child Health: A Literature Search, February 1973; Series 22 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Delivery of Health Care Services in Less Developed Countries, June 1973; Series 22 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Readings in Preventive Medicine, Undated; Series 22 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - The National Health Policy Forum: Education and Information Exchange for Washington Health Policymakers, September 1982; Series 22 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - New Directions in Managing and Funding Health Care Programs, December 31, 1982; Series 22 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - State Innovations in Health, March 30, 1980; Series 22 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Creating the Medical Marketplace: Selective Contracting in California's Medi-cal Program, July 1983; Series 22 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Second Careers: New Opportunities in Allied Health, Undated; Series 22 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - A Study of Nursing Homes and Related Facilities: Numbers and Ratios of Personnel within Long-term Care Institutions, November 1969; Series 22 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - A Study of Nursing Homes and Related Facilities: Characteristics of Administrators of Long-term Care Institutions, December 1969; Series 22 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - A Study of Nursing Homes and Related Facilities: Selected Institutional Characteristics of Long-term Care Facilities, January 1970; Series 22 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - A Study of Nursing Homes and Related Facilities: Selected Characteristics of Residents in Long-term Care Institutions, February 1970; Series 22 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - A Study of Nursing Homes and Related Facilities: The Evolution of Long-term Care in the United States, September 1969; Series 22 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Early Experiences with the Hazards of Medical Use of X-rays: 1896-1906, Undated; Series 22 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Health Effects of Low-level Ionizing Radiation: Final Report, July 1979; Series 22 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Final Report of Community Health Services and Facility Act: Project Grant Number CH 09-3 C-65, 1963-1966; Series 22 (Box 3, Folder 11)